Ki
[Music]
Record of drinking tea without sugar to keep wife company
Smiles are yours The one who
taught us to walk fast We have to make them big
Walking with them Hey Quiet Breaking the colors of happiness
Gautam Made new ones We would enjoy watching Papa's chosen stories
every time Your EAT
vada will increase back We have to surprise children of all ages
And keep
making new colors of happiness by reading them Gautam Keep making new
smiles throughout our
lives We make records of small and big
happiness of our loved ones For them, we have
ICICI Prudential Life Insurance
's Papers of Class so that they keep making happiness today, tomorrow and
always